Downloaded @ subs4free.club
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Our Father, who art
in Heaven, hallowed by thy name.
...be done, on Earth,
as it is in Heaven.
Forgive us our trespasses,
and lead us not into temptation.
But deliver us from evil.
Amen.
It's me.
By a richer parent,
in the name of our Lord,
Jesus Christ,
I command you
to give me your name.
You will submit
before the cross
of our high priest,
the creator
of heaven and Earth,
our one and only God,
Jesus Christ.
Give me your name!
Beleth.
We have its name...
Now we can read
the appropriate rites.
We expel the tormentor.
Beleth, deceiver
and unholy servant of Satan,
I command thee!
I order thee, Beleth,
abandon the body
and never again return
to torment its soul.
Beleth,
by the power of God...
You are too weak
to defeat me.
Beleth,
by the power of God,
return to the wasteland
he appointed you.
Aah!
Beleth, depart,
scum of Hell!
Depart!
Be gone in the name
of our Lord, Jesus Christ.
Be gone!
Mama.
Another demon vanquished,
another soul liberated.
God is good.
And the power of prayer,
your prayer, is great.
Join us again next week
to witness yet another miracle,
God willing.
In the meantime,
follow us @CleansingHour
and @FatherMaxTCH on social.
Thank you once again
for your support.
God bless you
and may the Devil miss you.
And cut!
Nice job, everybody!
Good show!
Hey, somebody get this guy
an Oscar, huh?
I'd like to thank
my mother-in-law
for the inspiration.
Well, thank you very much. Thank
you. Thanks. Appreciate it.
Hey, if you're going to
take any pictures,
do not
post them anywhere.
Thank you.
Nice show, man.
50,000 followers,
and I'm still not verified.
I'm never going to
be respected if I don't have
that little blue check mark
right next to my name.
Hey, did you, um, did you
read the e-mail I sent you?
The one
about branching out?
Did you read it?
Could you read it?
- Five million followers.
- Mm-hmm.
What I wouldn't do
for that kind of audience.
That's what I want
to talk to you about, okay?
I mean...
viewerships' peaked,
right?
Mm, you got to book
my boy Dante.
Drag queen, he...
she ... works at the bingo night
at the Bodice Lounge
as Scarlet von Cock.
Get it?
You get it?
Yeah, I get it.
Hey, I want to talk to you
about expansion.
Hey, who's drinking
with us tonight?!
We need to talk about expansion,
okay?
Ghost hunts, séances...
Drew?
Drew, we talked
about this, man.
- Priests don't do séances, bro.
- I know, I know.
But I got this girl.
She's great.
She's got her own stuff,
she won't...
Scarlett von Cock,
man.
She's fabulous,
okay?
Just book her.
Thomas, the bulk!
Mm!
Yeah, that thing right there
with the gurney was mm!
You ask,
I deliver.
I'm thinking we need a little
bit more pyro, though...
exploding lights,
uh, me silhouetted against
a shower of sparks,
like Clint Eastwood
or something.
Hell, yeah, love it.
Yo.
When's the show start?
Uh, Max,
meet my delightful niece,
Riley,
our new PA.
She's studying movies at SC,
where, apparently,
they don't use clocks.
Don't worry about that.
They gave me shit
about that all the time.
Like, we're artists.
We beat to our own drum.
I get it.
I love this whole look,
by the way.
It's very circa 2000s
Gwen Stefani.
You're working it.
What's the pay here?
Alright, Riles, why don't you go
and explore the set
and try not
to break anything.
Go.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Are you coming tonight?
Are you
gonna be there?
- I'll pass.
- Your boy's coming.
I'm not going.
Dude,
we never hang out anymore.
What do you
want me to do?
I got like
a ton of orders to fill.
Think of it
as brand management.
♪ You say I'm crazy, but I
really think I don't care ♪
♪ I might sound shady,
but I really want to go there ♪
♪ Give me no way out ♪
♪ Never mind a rain check ♪
You roll?
No, I'm good.
Go nuts.
- Okay, then.
- ♪ The long way, long way around ♪
♪ Stay up all night ♪
- ♪ Go all day long ♪
- You want to see some magic? Mm?
- Ah!
- So cool.
Magic.
- Mm-hmm.
♪ You tell them
where to go, go, go ♪
Oh, work it!
Yes!
♪ Stay up all night ♪
Am I supposed to know
who that is?
That's Father Max.
The famous exorcist?
He's no exorcist,
sweetheart.
Oh, so you've seen
the show?
♪ Stay up all night ♪
Then you don't
know shit, do you?
- Okay, let's go.
- Disgusting.
Alright, I'm going to need
a little back up
from my best friend, Drew.
Where are you, Drew?
Drew?
Everybody say, "Drew!"
Drew!
- Drew!
- Drew-ew-ew!
My best friend,
Drew!
There we go!
♪ Stay up all night ♪
♪ Go all day long ♪
♪ Want to do whatever we like ♪
♪ We want to do it
any time we want ♪
♪ When they tell you,
no, no, no ♪
♪ You tell them
where to go, go go ♪
♪ Stay up all night ♪
♪ And we can party
all day long ♪
Peace be with you.
Go, come on.
Don't be shy. Don't.
Excuse me,
Father Max.
Hi.
Um, I just
wanted to say that
we're, like,
your biggest fans.
Well,
bless your little hearts.
Can you sign
my prayer cloths?
Yeah.
Please, come, join us.
Hey, scoot over.
That's fine.
You guys sit down.
- This is Brenda.
- Hi.
I'm Desiree,
like, "desire,"
with an extra "E."
Cool!. Hey, you guys have fun.
I'm going to head home.
I'm going to go
fuck myself.
I am intrigued.
So, Father Max, um,
we're curious.
How does
a good-looking guy like yourself
take a vow of celibacy?
Well...
Well,
it can get very, very hard.
Are you really
a priest?
Think I lie to you?
I don't know.
I've just never met one
who's, you know, fun.
You think I'm fun, huh?
Ever since
I was a kid,
I wanted
to fight evil head on,
be on the front lines
of the spiritual world,
like the Archangel Michael.
Spent 10 years in school,
got ordained,
only to have
the church I love
deny
my singular ambition.
Being an exorcist.
So I quit.
Taught myself.
And you know what?
God's still with me.
I can feel it.
I can feel it, too.
Mm.
Do you wear a wig?
Aah!
What?
What did I do?
Oh, no, no.
You... You were good.
Do you want some... Do you want
some breakfast? You hungry?
You want
a homemade breakfast?
Thank you.
Show's plateaued,
man.
Can't grow an audience
without new content,
but Max will only do shows
that he can star in.
That's shocking.
Two, three...
I booked that zombie movie
with Jared Leto.
- Really?!
- First make-up assist.
Oh, my God!
That's awesome.
Mm!
Mm.
Oh, man, it is gonna suck
to lose you.
Maybe you should
quit the show, too.
What? Give up
on a thriving business?
Come on, we got
a wedding to pay for.
And besides,
I've known Max
since we were altar boys,
you know?
I can't just
abandon him.
I don't know if
he'd say the same about you.
You don't know him
like I do.
Wow!
Look at that.
Pops giving me the hard sell
with obsolete tech
that was never cool.
You know
what this should say?
This should say,
"Uproot your life.
Become
a corporate slave.
Love,
your Father.
P.S.
Mom misses you."
What?
I don't know.
Maybe the universe
is trying to tell you something.
Uh-huh.
I like being my own boss.
Max is the boss.
I don't think
he's the boss.
Oh!
That's pretty cool.
I can remote into work
with these.
That's not bad.
Hmm?
Nice?
Yeah.
This could work for me.
Ooh.
You look like
an asshole.
Thanks. Oh.
Look,
all I'm saying
is maybe you'd be happier
doing something on your own.
No.
All I have to do
is sell Max on expansion, okay?
Pivot his focus.
Max's focus is Max.
You're not
gonna change that.
I know this is hard
for you to hear,
but Max is using the show
as his meal ticket.
He doesn't care
about the business,
he doesn't care about you,
all the work you do.
You're getting played.
It's time
to pull the plug.
Dante, what's up?
It's, uh, Drew over at
"The Cleansing Hour."
Um, just calling to see
where you are.
Uh, give me...
give me a shout back.
Thanks.
Hey, come on.
Riley! Hey!
Delete that shit.
NDA, come on.
Riles, quit fucking around
and give me a hand.
What the fuck
are you doing?
Beautiful, isn't it?
God damn it!
Hey, buddy!
I'm looking for
14220 Hughes.
"The Cleansing Hour"?
Yeah.
Fuck this.
Oh, come on.
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
City of Angels my ass.
Makes you feel any better,
Max isn't here, either.
Yeah, well,
I expect him to be late.
Ahh.
I'm going to have to cancel.
Fuck.
Not a chance.
Yes, yes, yes!
You were in Drama Club.
- Drew.
- You were in Drama Club.
Max will have a total conniption
fit if we have to cancel.
Please,
it's not worth the fallout.
please, please?
Like, I'll literally...
like, please, baby?
Please? Please?
Please?
I need you
to do this.
You better sell
a lot of prayer cloths
- because our honeymoon...
- Mm-hmm.
...just moved
from Cabo to Bali.
Cool.
You're
a renaissance woman!
Bryce,
put it away.
So,
how was school today?
Learned about dinosaurs.
Ah,
your favorite.
What kind?
Triceratops
and pterodactyls.
Ah, cool!
The flying ones, right?
Yeah. Did you know
that their beaks were...
One second,
Bryce.
Yes?
Can you
give me an hour?
Yep, alright.
Sorry, kiddo.
Hold that thought.
I'll be right back.
Jung's cooking is almost
too beautiful to eat,
don't you think,
sweetie?
His nose
is kind of big.
"His nose is kind of big."
"He likes Nickelback."
"His hands
are too small."
Girl, give a dude a chance...
face-to-face.
Maybe even hip-to-hip.
I have standards.
I'm not just going to
hook up with some rando.
First off,
Father Max ain't no rando.
Second, without me,
you'd never leave the house.
And, third, a girl's
got to take charge these days.
All these pussy-assed dudes too
scared to buy a girl a drink.
- Hey, what's up?
- Good news!
Dr. Phil's looking for
a priest
to comment
on spiritual matters.
Praise God!
You're not thinking
of leaving, though, are you?
Don't worry, sinner. Daddy's
just spreading his wings.
- Where's Lane?
- Lane, she's... she's...
- Lane! I need her to cover this zit, alright?
- Changing.
She's changing. We got
some stuff we got to talk...
- You booked Dante?
- I did.
- I've been trying to call him, but I...
- I have to show you.
Remember that chick
from the, uh, karaoke bar?
- Mm-hmm.
- Ah! Ah, yes! Ah!
Cool.
- I got a groupie.
- Yeah.
- No, cool.
- I got a disciple.
Cool! Awesome!
Here,
here's your script.
What were you trying to say
about tonight's show?
- On in three!
- Max!
Ready for
your blessing?
You alright there,
Chris?
Just late night.
Uh, can you give me
a mike check?
Mike check, one, two,
one, two, one, two.
Jesus!
Oh, my...
Ooh!
How about partying
after work, huh?
Go clean yourself up.
Ah,
this is so weird.
So, I'm going to talk you
through everything in the IFB.
Okay.
And I need
to take that.
- Okay.
- You sure about this?
You know what?
I think I've changed my mind.
That's not funny.
Thank you.
Alright.
Hey, kid, you want
to see something cool?
Wah!
What's
The Devil's Database?
This baby right here
is a digital encyclopedia
of every demon
known to man.
It's got authentic
character traits,
descriptions, history,
it's got exorcism prayers.
I mean, it's a work in progress,
but it's actually
a hell of a lot easier than
digging through all of that.
Please don't
touch that!
You don't stream
in 4K?
That's ghetto.
Yeah, why don't you, uh,
you go stand by your uncle, hmm?
Thanks.
Careful, please!
Please, just...
that's the snake.
That's what carries
our signal.
Please be careful.
Oh, those are
actually called "stingers."
Just FYI.
Wow! Laney,
doing stand-in work now.
Look, if you need
a little bit of money,
don't be afraid to ask.
Alright, let's get
this thing started.
- Where's my queen?
- You're looking at her.
Drew,
where's Dante?
She bailed, man.
No. No, no way.
She's not an actress.
She doesn't even know
the lines.
It'll be fine. It's what
we have the monitors for.
She looks like
every other possessed chick
we've ever had,
alright?
We need shock value,
pizzazz.
I'll be fine.
I have to look
at your face for an hour.
It's more than enough
to make a girl homicidal.
Hey, Lane or no-show,
amigo.
You got 10 seconds.
Follow the monitors.
Let me lead.
Alright, here we go,
and three, two.
Good evening, my followers.
Welcoming to
"The Cleansing Hour."
I'm Father Max, your guide
and faithful servant
in a fallen world.
Follow me on
social @FatherMaxTCH.
Cleansing Hour.
Max, come on, you got to...
@CleansingHour.
Tonight, we bring you Sabrina,
a tortured soul
from a broken home,
molested by her stepfather,
beaten by her mother.
Sabrina escaped her pain
through drugs, alcohol,
and, ultimately,
prostitution.
The enemy of God
exploited her frailty
and took control of her body,
but tonight, with your prayers
and my leadership,
Sabrina will be rid
of this evil.
The molested ones
are always jacked.
Yeah, she gonna
flip a dick.
Alright, Lane, now writhe
for me a little bit
like there's an itch
you can't scratch.
Good, good, good.
Now, it feels like
there's something menacing
creeping inside of you.
It's like
a feeling you dread,
like a start
of a bad dream.
And line.
Help me, Father Max.
Please.
I can feel it.
It's inside of me.
That's good,
that's good.
Just like that.
Keep your head down.
What they can't see
will terrify them.
Alright, Max,
let's work in the merch.
Tonight, my child,
you will witness
the healing power of prayer,
both by my utterance
and holy linen
from the Vatican.
Lord have mercy
on us.
Christ have mercy
Lord have mercy
on us.
Lights.
This demon already manifests
electromagnetic disturbances.
We could be dealing with
a Stage Four possession.
I command
the unclean spirit,
by the mysteries
of the incarnation,
passion, resurrection,
and ascension.
You tell me your name
and obey me to the letter.
Your name, demon.
Speak!
My God!
You're a natural.
Tell me your name.
In the name of our Lord,
Jesus Christ.
Boom, Chris.
Chris?
We're seeing the boom.
You said
you were fine.
Get up, now!
What the fuck
is that thing?
Max, Max, Max!
Get back on camera.
Riley, get the boom.
Chris, splash some water on
your face and sober the fuck up!
Okay.
Okay, keep it together.
You just took some bad shit.
This'll pass.
What? What?
Holy shit, what?
What, what, what?
Abhorrent slime of hell,
give me your name!
Alright, baby,
that's your cue. Paimon.
This demon has no respect
for God's authority.
Perhaps a larger dose of holy
water will force compliance.
Hey, Lane, uh,
Max is better on script, babe,
so why don't you... don't you
just follow his lead?
Speak, child.
What is
the demon telling you?
This is tight.
What was that?
Louder, my dear.
This is tight.
It's okay.
You can whisper it
to me.
This is tight.
Shit, Lane,
what are you doing?
Max,
are you alright?
No, no, no, Max!
Max, we're live.
We're live.
Breathe.
Just breathe, man.
You will submit to me
before the cross of our Lord!
Tell me your name,
worm of Gehenna!
Tell me your name.
I'm gonna make you
work for it, Maxi.
What did
you just call me?
Lane,
what's, uh, going on?
Tommy, come here.
What are you doing?
I don't know, man,
just go with it.
Lane, if this is about me
leaving dishes in the sink,
there's a better way
to get back at me.
Nice ink.
What are you,
some kind of tough guy?
Um...
I'm not really qualified
to address demons.
That's best left
to the professionals, right?
Mm,
birds of a feather.
Is there
a French flag emoji?
What? Man, what the fuck?
What the fuck?
Looks like the show's
got some heat, Maxi.
Time to go
off script.
Somebody, please, help!
This is very real!
We're at 14220...
Drop out.
Drew!
Tonight, Father, you'll have
a chance to save your own soul.
If you don't, I'll kill
sweet little Sabrina here
in a way that makes Tommy's
death look like euthanasia.
Drew, cut the feed at any point,
I kill the girl.
Max, you step off set
at any point, I kill the girl.
Anyone tries to run...
I'll kill you.
You have 49 minutes
to lift the veil.
Oh, help me, please!
Get me out of here!
Drew! Drew!
Ah, ah, ah!
What the fuck?
It's only Max
in the limelight now.
You step on set
and she dies.
Let her go,
scum of Hell!
She doesn't deserve this.
Take me instead.
Do you really
mean that, Maxi?
Do you really want to see
what she sees
and feel
what she feels?
This is the defining moment
of your life.
Do penance
or become a martyr.
So...
do you want me?
- Okay.
- Why are you here?
To see
if you're a bona fide saint
or a whitewash,
too.
What?
You fuck
with the bull,
you'll eventually
get the horns.
Summon it now,
demon!
- It's not gonna work.
- The God's word.
The Lord is my shepherd,
I shall not...
Max, that's not
gonna work!
Yea, though I walk
through the valley of...
Max, it's not
gonna work!
You can't just read
random Bible verses.
There's specific rites
for each demon.
We need its name.
Yeah. Yeah.
In the name of our Lord,
Jesus Christ,
I command you
to tell me your name!
Your fans
deserve better.
Alright, loyal followers,
you decide.
How should Father Max
#SaveSabrina?
Your wish
is his command.
You had
your chance.
You know
we could have shared him.
I'm a good girl.
Oh,
you a freak-a-leek.
Yeah.
My friends,
this isn't a game.
It's a battle between good
and evil, life and death!
I need prayers.
I need wholesome thoughts.
Whatever happened to,
"With your prayers
and my leadership,
Sabrina will be rid
of this evil."
Max,
I got an idea.
Keep this asshole talking,
get more info.
How do I do that?
Do what you do best, man...
bullshit.
You talk a big game
for someone
who picks on an innocent girl.
Nobody's innocent.
You're a bully, a coward
who picks on the weak.
This isn't why
people tune in.
They tune in
to see good prevail,
to see
your kind defeated.
So, defeat me.
Forgive them, Lord,
they know not what they do.
God made them
this way.
Must be
part of his plan.
What do you know
of God's plan,
other than
how to corrupt it?
I was there
when he wrote it.
That's great, Max.
That's great, that's great.
Keep it up.
Time's up!
Drew,
what's it gonna be?
We're up a creek, man,
and we got everything
from disgusting to illegal here.
And there's no way
I'm letting you touch Lane.
Most innocent suggestion...
...strip.
There's got to be
something else. Come on, man.
I don't know.
- Shirt off.
- No.
I won't do it.
No!
Then the girl dies.
Hey, it's fine. I'm going to
keep you in a tight shot.
Nobody's going to
see anything.
What is going on?
I'm not doing that.
I'm not doing that, Max.
Oh,
proof there is a God.
Mm-hmm.
Um, hey!
Alright,
you had your fun.
Hardly.
You know the moves.
Come on!
Sabrina and half a million
viewers are counting on you.
Show some enthusiasm.
Okay.
Oh,
that's so cool!
What on earth
is this devilry?
You might as well call upon
Satan directly.
Not in my classroom!
The Act of Contrition,
Andrew.
Oh my God, I am heartily sorry
for having offended thee.
I detest all my sins because of
thy just punishments,
but most of all
because they offend thee.
My God, who art all good
and deserving of all my love,
I firmly resolve with the help
of they grace to sin no more
and avoid
the near occasion of sin.
Maxi.
My God,
I'm sorry...
Heartily sorry.
Again.
My God,
I'm heartily sorry because...
For having offended you.
Again!
My God, I detest
all my sins.
Again!
Well,
you didn't save Sabrina...
but you certainly
drew a crowd.
Oh, my God, Max!
We need to see.
You alright?
Yeah.
We got to figure out
which demon this is
and what it wants.
Clearly, it wants
to make a fool out of me.
No, no, no.
No, there's got to be
a bigger play.
Either way, it's gonna kill Lane
if we don't hurry.
Basustai...
maybe that's something?
Before it headbutted you,
it said, "Basustai."
I studied ancient languages
in prep school.
It means "lies."
Demons lie.
No shit.
Well, that's something.
Riley, good job.
Max,
you can use that.
You can use it.
Come on!
I am willing to do
your bidding.
Lie for you.
Just tell me what you want
so we can end this.
Maybe I already have.
Don't listen to it!
Shut up, bitch!
Drew!
Lane,
talk to me, baby.
It wants...
I'll snap your neck like a twig.
She's fighting back.
Come on, Lane, fight, babe!
Come on!
It won't let me.
She's... She's choking.
She's choking!
She's choking, Max!
- I mean, what do I do?
- I can do the Heimlich
if you could just
get her out of the chair.
- No, it could be a trap.
- Come on, stop talking about it!
She's gonna die.
Fucking do something!
Max!
Alright, alright! Riley,
hold her head. Hold her head.
I'm gonna clear
the airway.
I feel something.
Fuck,
she's turning blue, man.
Here, I got it.
I got it.
Pull it out!
What the fuck is that?
What?
Hey, baby, you alright?
You alright?
- Cut the feed.
- Can't, babe, it will kill you.
You have to.
It's one of ours.
I-I don't get it,
man.
Oh, my God!
Basustai, ba-basustai, basustai.
Max, Max, it wants us to
tell the truth about the merch.
- What?
- Call it a hunch, man.
Oh.
I will not sully my good name
based on a hunch, okay?
- I won't do it anymore.
- Listen to me. Listen to me!
The woman that I love
is fucking dying
and you're worried
about staying in character?
You shut the fuck up!
You tell the truth, or I swear
to God, I fucking will.
Go.
Go!
This better work.
My friend...
I have something
that's been weighing
heavily on my heart.
You see, the prayer cloths...
See, the prayer cloths...
they have no healing power,
okay?
They're not even
from the Vatican.
They're just
some cheap crap from China.
It's working. It's working.
It's fucking working.
And the holy water is just...
it's from my bathroom sink.
Alright?
But, okay, but understand,
alright?
It wasn't my idea, alright?
My producer...
Max!
Max, the truth, man!
Yeah, okay, okay!
I knew better, alright,
and I went with it all along.
The love of money
is the root of evil,
and I fell prey
to the temptation.
I'm so ashamed. I'm so ashamed.
But, please, forgive me.
Lane, hey, baby. Hey, baby.
Lane, are you alright?
- I want to go home.
- I know you do.
I know you do. I know you do.
I want to get you home.
Think about those
crystal-clear waters
and white powder beaches
in Bali, baby.
Come on,
we're gonna be there soon.
No, God, fuck!
Come on!
- Come on!
- I told you, man! I fucking told you!
Just shut up!
Check her fucking throat!
Oh, my God!
Max. Max!
I'm trying!
I'm trying! I'm trying!
Come on.
Fuck!
Max, it's not after
your confession.
It's after mine.
For the last year,
I've been keeping
the lion's share of the profits.
60%. 70%.
Look, this whole fucking show
runs because of me.
I get here early,
I stay late.
All you have to do
is show up.
That's how I rationalize
keeping the money.
I'm sorry,
man.
It's okay, my son.
I forgive you.
You're paying me back
with interest.
Fuck this!
I'll call someone.
No, I got this.
Loose hose,
I think.
Maybe the brake line?
Maybe the driver.
Oh, fuck.
This is gonna hurt, bud.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I can do it.
I can do it!
Hey!
Do you want to bleed out?
Do you want
to bleed out?
Come on.
So many sins,
so little time.
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
You'd make
a great nurse.
Yeah?
You'd make a pretty corpse.
Boy Scouts.
First Aid merit badge.
That's right.
You did mine
for me.
I did. I did.
So we'd make Eagle Scouts
together.
What am I gonna do,
man?
What am I gonna do?
This thing knows us.
All our sins.
We confess,
we live.
- Confess what?
- I don't know.
We got to listen
for more clues.
Shit!
Shit, shit,
shit, shit!
Oh, shit.
Max,
we're losing signal.
We got major loss.
I think the servers
must be overwhelmed
from all the viewers.
So, fix it.
- Oh, no.
- Hey, what's the Wi-Fi password?
What is going on?
Give me
some good news, Drew.
I suppose it's time
to say goodbye
to the audience
and to your friends.
Oh, my God.
What happened
to your hand?
It's local.
It's local, it's local.
Drew!
Oh, shit.
Where's he going?
He's going to
fix the signal.
The feed's
about to drop.
Don't do it!
Let it go!
I'm not gonna let you die.
Oh, shit.
Please,
come back.
Just be here with me
when it happens.
Stop it, Lane!
You don't want to die.
There's a bigger plan here,
Drew.
Let me out.
Yeah, I might just
give you a hand.
Please, Max.
Yeah, you think I'm gonna
really fall for that?
- Max.
- Huh?
It's me.
- Ah!
- It's Lane.
Please!
I saw it.
What?
The beast.
I love you, Drew.
Good job, buddy.
Chris! Hey!
Wake up!
I'm sorry, man.
I fucked up.
What are you talking about?
Sorry for what?
I'll never be high
at work again, I swear.
I don't give a shit right now.
Look at me.
You may be able
to save us.
I need you to tell me
what you saw.
Save us?
From what?
Tell them the truth.
...now and at the hour
of our death.
Amen.
Very good,
Andrew.
Holy Mother delivers us
from all peril.
Maxi?
You can do it.
Hail Mary,
full of grace.
Don't help him,
you miserable cheat!
Hail Mary, full of grace.
The Lord is with thee.
- Shut up!
- Blessed art thou among women...
- Stop it!
- Stop it! You're hurting him!
- ...fruit of thy womb, Jesus.
- Oh, you little wretch.
You must learn
some respect.
Stop it!
You're hurting him!
- Don't! He's my friend!
- Shut up!
Blessed art thou
among women...
Stop! Stop it!
Stop it! No!
Maxi?
Hey! Get out of it!
Pull it together!
Look at me.
Look at me!
Focus!
Take a breath.
You said you saw a beast
in the chair, right?
Describe it to me.
Fucking scary,
man.
No shit!
What did it look like?
Ah, Drew!
Look out!
What the fuck?
That's it!
Pull your shit together
or we're going to fucking die!
- Do you understand me?!
- Yeah.
Okay.
Okay, I'm cool.
It was like a bird or something
with fangs and shit.
Good.
What else?
A-A hairy body.
Kind of like a dog.
And a big-ass tail,
like a big snake.
Arms, legs?
I don't know, uh,
part man, part goat.
- Ugly shit.
- Okay. Okay. Good.
Hey,
what else can I do?!
Just you stay here.
Oh, no, no!
Don't leave me here!
Alright.
Max, I got some good news.
Check the monitor.
It's not real.
It's just your imagination.
Oh, it's not real.
Get off! Get off!
What?!
There's something
in there.
You guys
have got to help me.
Let's get
out of here. Hide!
Hey! Hey!
Relax, there's nothing there.
What the hell
is going on?!
What is it,
man?
Yes, Chris,
describe them for us.
Nancy Drew will
tell us their names.
Okay,
you shut the fuck up!
Oh, God!
- Oh, oh! Oh, oh! Oh my God!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Hey, hey, hey!
- You mean you guys aren't seeing this?
Take it easy, man.
Hey!
What the fuck
is that?!
- Don't let them get me, man!
- Chris!
Don't let them get me!
Don't let them fucking get me!
Chris!
Hey, hey, Max!
You got to confess something,
man.
Anything.
I-I took
offering money once.
I-I...
I hit my neighbor's car
and I didn't leave a note.
I don't know,
man!
Hey!
What the fuck are you doing?
What the fuck
are you doing?
Our Holy Mother delivers us
from all peril.
You got to pray
with me.
Come here.
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee.
Blessed are thou
amongst women,
and blessed is the fruit
of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary,
Mother of God,
pray for us sinners now
and at the hour of our death.
- Amen.
- Yeah.
You got to say,
"Amen."
Amen.
It worked.
It worked, man!
It worked!
Friends, never underestimate
the power of prayer.
Or the power
of denial.
- Chris!
- Oh, no, get him off me!
Chris!
No, no, Chris!
Don't! Chris! Chris!
- Chris! Chris!
- Oh, shit!
No, no! Chris!
God, stop!
Knock it the fuck off!
- Chris!
- Fuck!
Don't do drugs, kids.
I don't get it.
I prayed.
I got every word right.
My patience and your time
are running out.
What do you want
from me?!
Ahh.
You want me
to kill myself.
I want you
to unburden your conscience.
Since your value
your public perception
more than human life,
let us once again
let the viewers
decide your fate.
You can keep your life
if you keep it 100.
Do they have the heart
to save you?
Okay.
Hey.
Just remember
why people watch.
Alright,
it's for your charm,
it's for your bravery,
and for your good looks.
Just give them
what they want.
You can do it...
Father Max.
I have faith in my followers.
Fuck.
Get your phone.
Get your phone!
My loyal followers,
I stand before you
a defeated man.
After countless victories
over evil...
I think I've met my match.
A force has overpowered me...
murdered my crew.
My friends.
Now it looks like I'm next,
unless you have mercy on me.
Hey, keep going.
Keep going.
What are you looking at?
Focus!
I'm a sinner.
We all are.
But do we deserve to die for it?
What makes us... human?
Tell them the truth,
Maxi.
Cast the first stone.
God hates
disobedient children.
Love the sinner, hate the sin.
- My God, I'm sorry.
- Heartily sorry!
You're a stupid
little boy.
My God,
I'm heartily sorry.
Again!
Go on, Max.
You can do it.
Go on, Maxi.
Lie to them again.
- Again!
- Stop!
- The Lord is with me.
- Again!
I detest all my sins.
- No!
I don't want to die.
Again!
- You can do it.
- Again.
Again!
I can't!
It's alright.
Just go with your gut.
I'm a phony. I'm a fraud.
Everything you think
you know about me is just...
made up.
It's part of a character.
"The Cleansing Hour"...
every episode is just a hoax.
It's a big act.
Except for tonight.
Isn't that obvious by now?
I'm no priest.
What?
I was.
I was raised Roman Catholic,
and they say,
"If you want to do right by God,
you got to follow the rules."
"Do this, don't do that.
Recite this prayer.
Sit. Stand. Kneel."
I... I was never good at it.
I was kind of a dumb kid,
but it doesn't take smarts...
to know what evil is,
and hell if I wasn't
gonna stand up to her.
Stop it!
You're hurting him!
Stop! He's my friend!
- Stop! Stop it!
- Stop it!
Shut up, you little wretch.
You miserable cheat!
She haunted me for years,
through high school, college.
I just chalked it up
to God punishing me
for what I had done.
Order up!
That's why I went
into seminary.
Got ordained,
thinking maybe, somehow,
if I just devoted my life
to following God's rules,
he'd forgive me.
But I'm...
The closer I got to the Church,
the more hypocrisy
and corruption that I saw.
The so-called keys to Heaven
were being held
by perverts and con men,
the very evil I wanted to fight.
What kind of God
would allow that scandal?
So, I quit the Church,
quit believing in their lies.
Figured that there's no God,
so I could live
by my own rules...
pick on somebody else.
Who?
All I ever knew was
religious rituals,
labelism, and prayers.
So...
So, me and my best friend...
we started this show.
I didn't think
it mattered it was fake.
People loved it.
People loved me.
Once again...
there's blood on my hands...
because of my foolishness.
I don't deserve it.
I beg of you...
please...
forgive me for what I've done.
Looks like a Hail Mary
couldn't save you
this time either, Maxi!
But I told them everything.
Mobs don't care
about the truth.
I won't do it!
If you want me dead,
you're gonna have
to do it yourself!
Lane? Lane! Lane!
Lane!
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no!
Lane, no!
No!
No! No!
I'm sorry.
No! No! No!
No!
Stop!
Drew?
Wait, baby!
Lane, hey.
Hey, talk to me.
It's okay.
I'm listening.
You're okay.
Talk to me.
You're getting played.
It's time
to pull the plug.
Let him go, motherfucker,
or I'll cut the cameras.
don't!
It'll kill her!
It won't.
It needs a vessel.
It needs you.
It needs the confessions.
It needs the torture.
'Cause it's all
to drive up viewership,
Isn't that right?!
Flex your muscles
in front of a crowd.
Demon defeats priest,
cosmic fucking payback.
No? Nothing?
okay, how about this?
Boom! There you go.
Dead air!
Nobody gives a shit what you do
to us if they can't see it.
Ah, ah!
Ah, ah, ah!
Come on.
Come on, come on!
Thank God! Yes!
Clever little bitch,
isn't she?
Now restore the picture.
No!
You're in no position
to bargain.
The only way
you get through this
is to turn those cameras
back on, now!
Fuck you!
Everything out
of your mouth has been a lie,
and why should
we believe you now?
It's just going to kill us
anyway, idn't that right?
From fake priest
to false prophet.
You got it all figured out,
don't you?
I see the writing
on the wall.
But I see everything!
Shit.
We got it!
You ready to save the day,
my friend?
You know what?
Restore the feed.
Yeah?
I want the world
to see this.
Oh, God!
It says here
he's a Marquis of Hell,
governs 40 infernal legions.
Oh my God,
no wonder he's so powerful.
I don't give a shit.
Send me the rites, man.
Come on.
Shit! I haven't put them in yet.
Give me a second.
This one. This one.
Here we go.
Come on.
Commander...
You know, Maxi, now that
we've got our audience back,
I think we can hold our own
these last few minutes.
Three's a crowd, right?
Drew, watch out!
Ah!
Mmm, mmm, mmm,
that'll just shock yourself.
Let him go, please!
Lift the veil!
Or you could just let him die
and you can go free.
I don't what more to say!
You do!
And so does the girl.
Oh, my God.
What's going on?
Drew! Max, help him!
It wants another confession.
- What?
- It says we both know.
Oh! Oh!
Mm-hmm.
Oh, I, um...
What?
Oh.
Oh, my God.
A long time ago,
before you and I met,
Max and I...
- Ah!
- It was short-lived.
He...
You motherfucker!
Ah!
How could you keep that from me?
Drew, I ghosted her, man.
I was a total fucking dick.
You know me, alright?
She already hated me
by the time you hired her,
and I didn't want
to put us at odds, alright?
I'd never seen you
so fucking happy.
I had a right to know!
I was going to tell you,
I swear,
but I had just met and I put
it off until it was just...
Ancient history, man.
Meant to be forgotten.
Ah!
Mmm!
Baby, hey, look at me.
Don't let this
come between us.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Oh, no.
Right, now let him go!
Ah.
What?
What...
what's that?
Oh, shit!
What?
It's a wrong number.
What is that?
Shut up!
Hey!
I hate being on camera.
Stop!
The camera
loves you though.
Mm-hmm.
Oh! Very nice!
Pose for me.
Oh!
That's perty, isn't it?
I'll show you...
You told me you deleted that,
you piece of shit!
I thought I did.
Drew.
Let me explain, man.
What's up? You saving that
for a lonely night?
I swear to God I never
watch it, dude. I swear!
Just like
the karaoke chick, yeah?
How many pictures and videos
of my soon-to-be wife
do you have
on your phone?
Cocksucker.
You know, I don't know
what's worse,
the thought of you rubbing
one out to my wife
or the fact that
you fucking use everybody.
You're a fucking leech!
This is what it wants.
To drive us apart.
I like the way it thinks.
You know all of my life,
all my life I treated you
like a brother!
And for what?
Drew.
Bullshit! You never cared
about anybody but yourself,
you conceited fuck!
Drew,
you're going to kill him.
Yeah, go on, kill him.
I'll release you
and the girl.
- It's okay.
- Man, don't do it.
Push the button.
- What?
- Push the god damn button!
Come on!
Commander of legions
and all the servants
that you control that you.
You can't defeat me!
Fuck you!
And by the power
of the Almighty...
Shit!
Max,
You got to take over!
And the power of the Almighty
and the hand of his son,
Lord, Jesus Christ.
You and your army shall be
swept away to the pit of glory
where you will forever
lay your heads.
Depart, Aamon, and depart
servile demons from this vessel,
for her future and past
are not in your hands,
but in the arms of the
Sovereign Lord God Almighty.
It is he and he alone
who brought the world
into being.
Numbers of
and know the day
that our soul takes flight.
Thus humble yourself demon.
You are helpless
before your creator.
Get this thing off me!
Drew, wait!
Lane?
Lane, Lane.
I'm here, baby.
Oh, shit!
Drew! Drew, what do I do?
Keep reading!
For under his command
and his command alone.
In the name of Jesus Christ,
make haste and
Drew, what are you doing?
You're hurting me!
Oh, fuck you, bitch!
The monster of the wretched
hell, tarry not
and return to your master,
the Prince of Darkness.
In the name of Jesus Christ,
I bind you and your army,
to cast you out
from this place.
Ah!
Drew, I didn't finish!
Go ahead.
Finish me.
What are you waiting for?
Five minutes to kill.
Any ideas?
Go fuck yourself.
The power of the holy spirit
compress this vessel and
creation of the Almighty God,
who casts a white light of
purity at which you cower.
Retreat now, Aamon, into desolation.
Gravel at the feet
of your lord savior
in the void of the pain
Amen.
Lane? Lane?
- No, no, no, no, no!
- No, no!
- Hey!
- No!
Hey! Hey! It's me.
It's me. It's me.
It's okay.
Hey, listen.
I just want to say...
No.
No, like, please, okay?
I know I don't deserve it.
No!
Not another word.
What am I supposed
to do now, huh?
Well, we're still live.
Ask your groupies.
Okay.
- Ah!
- Holy shit!
That can't be.
It was supposed to work.
- We said all of Aamon's rites.
- No.
You are no man of God,
and I am not Aamon.
We... we narrowed down
all the names.
We wrote the names...
all the names on the list.
It was my list.
What's The Devil's Database?
This baby right here
is a digital encyclopedia
of every demon
known to man.
Oh, God!
He's not here right now.
Oh, Maxi.
It's much too late for that.
Drew, cut the feed!
Cut the feed! Cut the feed!
Lane!
Oh, why me?
Why us?
We have started
our descent into Mumbai.
Come on! Come on!
Come on, Lane!
Lane, no! Come on!
Call an ambulance!
Come on, Lane! Come on, baby!
Come on, come on.
Come on, come on!
Come back. Come back.
There you go. There you go.
Shh, shh.
No, no, no, don't get up. Don't get up.
It's okay. You're okay.
You're okay.
What happened?
I don't.
I was hoping
you could tell us.
The whole time you were...
you were telling us
to... to cut the feed.
There's more to it
than that, isn't there?
Mm?
I can't remember.
Please tell me
he's in there holding the pen.
Yes, but he's cranky.
He missed dinner again.
Shit.
Hey, little guy!
You here to see your Daddy?
I think it's better
to let him in.
Somebody wanted to say
goodnight, Mr. President.
Hey, bud.
What are you still doing up?
- Look out!
- Bryce!
- Get off me!
- What are you...
- Aah!
Show's canceled.
Now what?
We need units here now!
Shots fired! Shots fired!
Send backup now
to 1200 Washington!
And 12 passengers
broke into the cockpit,
attacked the pilot.
Nosedived into a field
just outside Mumbai.
Authorities
have not ruled out terrorism.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull